[
  {
    "id": "T8D01",
    "correct": 3,
    "question": "Which of the following is a digital communications mode?",
    "answers": [
      "Packet radio",
      "IEEE 802.11",
      "FT8",
      "All these choices are correct"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": "T8D02",
    "correct": 1,
    "question": "What is a “talkgroup” on a DMR repeater?",
    "answers": [
      "A group of operators sharing common interests",
      "A way for groups of users to share a channel at different times without hearing other users on the channel",
      "A protocol that increases the signal-to-noise ratio when multiple repeaters are linked together",
      "A net that meets at a specified time"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": "T8D03",
    "correct": 3,
    "question": "What kind of data can be transmitted by APRS?",
    "answers": [
      "GPS position data",
      "Text messages",
      "Weather data",
      "All these choices are correct"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": "T8D04",
    "correct": 2,
    "question": "What type of transmission is indicated by the term \"NTSC?\"",
    "answers": [
      "A Normal Transmission mode in Static Circuit",
      "A special mode for satellite uplink",
      "An analog fast-scan color TV signal",
      "A frame compression scheme for TV signals"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": "T8D05",
    "correct": 0,
    "question": "Which of the following is an application of APRS?",
    "answers": [
      "Providing real-time tactical digital communications in conjunction with a map showing the locations of stations",
      "Showing automatically the number of packets transmitted via PACTOR during a specific time interval",
      "Providing voice over internet connection between repeaters",
      "Providing information on the number of stations signed into a repeater"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": "T8D06",
    "correct": 1,
    "question": "What does the abbreviation \"PSK\" mean?",
    "answers": [
      "Pulse Shift Keying",
      "Phase Shift Keying",
      "Packet Short Keying",
      "Phased Slide Keying"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": "T8D07",
    "correct": 0,
    "question": "Which of the following describes DMR?",
    "answers": [
      "A technique for time-multiplexing two digital voice signals on a single 12.5 kHz repeater channel",
      "An automatic position tracking mode for FM mobiles communicating through repeaters",
      "An automatic computer logging technique for hands-off logging when communicating while operating a vehicle",
      "A digital technique for transmitting on two repeater inputs simultaneously for automatic error correction"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": "T8D08",
    "correct": 3,
    "question": "Which of the following is included in packet radio transmissions?",
    "answers": [
      "A check sum that permits error detection",
      "A header that contains the call sign of the station to which the information is being sent",
      "Automatic repeat request in case of error",
      "All these choices are correct"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": "T8D09",
    "correct": 3,
    "question": "What is CW?",
    "answers": [
      "A type of electromagnetic propagation",
      "A digital mode used primarily on 2 meter FM",
      "A technique for coil winding",
      "Another name for a Morse code transmission"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": "T8D10",
    "correct": 3,
    "question": "Which of the following operating activities is supported by digital mode software in the WSJT-X software suite?",
    "answers": [
      "Earth-Moon-Earth",
      "Weak signal propagation beacons",
      "Meteor scatter",
      "All these choices are correct"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": "T8D11",
    "correct": 2,
    "question": "What is an ARQ transmission system?",
    "answers": [
      "A special transmission format limited to video signals",
      "A system used to encrypt command signals to an amateur radio satellite",
      "An error correction method in which the receiving station detects errors and sends a request for retransmission",
      "A method of compressing data using autonomous reiterative Q codes prior to final encoding"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": "T8D12",
    "correct": 0,
    "question": "Which of the following best describes an amateur radio mesh network?",
    "answers": [
      "An amateur-radio based data network using commercial Wi-Fi equipment with modified firmware",
      "A wide-bandwidth digital voice mode employing DMR protocols",
      "A satellite communications network using modified commercial satellite TV hardware",
      "An internet linking protocol used to network repeaters"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": "T8D13",
    "correct": 1,
    "question": "What is FT8?",
    "answers": [
      "A wideband FM voice mode",
      "A digital mode capable of low signal-to-noise operation",
      "An eight channel multiplex mode for FM repeaters",
      "A digital slow-scan TV mode with forward error correction and automatic color compensation"
    ]
  }
]